{
    "id": "f7d7820686eb488ba182fe9c585546cb",
    "title": "Do, Does And Did Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "..................... you know where he is going?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Do",
                "Does",
                "Did"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1e2a8ac3809143dc8ae1007a52bf2cfb"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. she understand the importance of working hard?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Do",
                "Does",
                "Did"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "31e3f5bda7f943038178eec5ee60848b"
        },
        {
            "question": "..................... they hold all-night parties?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Do",
                "Does",
                "Did"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3c385bf573ee4bd38ab78d7a951608fe"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where ..................... they live?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does",
                "did"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "22d6ef1a8cbd4ebdaf21a23f5108227a"
        },
        {
            "question": "How …………………. you operate this washing machine?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does",
                "did"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b661715b22f7452f85a3c04a71cb3a38"
        },
        {
            "question": "What ………………… you do then?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does",
                "did"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f415dc7b81ac42108333acfcaf4157f7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………. not know that I was playing with fire.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did",
                "do",
                "does"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1ab88c4459394a52a67e0e6ea755e1af"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. she say anything when you told her that you were leaving?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Do",
                "Does",
                "Did"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9e2f9c13692540099fde18640e839e30"
        },
        {
            "question": "Samuel ………………… not work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does",
                "did"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7a474f68e38f49259d79d6884dc78583"
        },
        {
            "question": "Martha and Samuel …………………. not appreciate the dignity of labor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does",
                "did"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "48c39326cd6e4bfa849fab77b81ddbe8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Peter ………………….. not know the answer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does",
                "do",
                "did"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4ac2ac4cf2b34d13a4c1bcf73f3f7034"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ..................... not like children who ……………. not respect their elders.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do, do",
                "does, does",
                "did, does"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6aff520316c0478abbcc5f9b9f75c175"
        }
    ]
}